couponsaregreat.net 2012-11-13

# disclosure and privacy policy

**Here are the two big bullet points I know I always look for:**

  * We respect your privacy.  Any information we collect about you will not be shared.  The only exception is if you win a giveaway we may need to pass your information along to the sponsor or representing PR agency.
  * Some of our posts, links, and banners will include affiliate or referral links. We appreciate your support of our site.  Many times we reinvest what is made back in to the site.

**Material Connection Disclosure**

Unless otherwise expressly stated, you should assume that _Coupons Are Great_ has an affiliate relationship or other material connection to the providers of goods and services mentioned by, recommended, hyperlinked to, or otherwise referenced on _Coupons Are Great_. In addition, you should assume that _Coupons Are Great_ may be compensated monetarily or non-monetarily when you visit, purchase goods or services from, or take any other action on a third-party website mentioned by, recommended, hyperlinked to, or otherwise referenced on Coupons Are Great. You should always perform due diligence before buying any goods or services online or offline.

**This policy is valid from 10 November 2010**

This blog is a collaborative blog written by a group of individuals. For questions about this blog, please contact Leandrea At CouponsAreGreat Dot Net.

This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, paid insertions or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

To get your own policy, go to http://www.disclosurepolicy.org

### Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Terms of Use**

We are not infallible.  Sometimes we make mistakes.  We will not be held accountable if we make a mistake.  We make no claims about the correctness of any data on this website.  We make nor warranty that anything on this website works correctly.  This web site could contain technical or other mistakes, inaccuracies, or typographical errors.  We assume no responsibility for errors or omissions in this website.

In no event shall we be liable to you or any third parties for special, punitive, incidental, indirect, or consequential damages of any kind, or damages whatsoever, including, without limitation, those resulting from your use of information or data obtained from this site.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.couponsaregreat.net

Alpharetta, GA 30004 USA

feedback@couponsaregreat.net

This policy was last modified on May 4th, 2011

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
